接着转  接着转
And turn. And turn.
- 接着转  接着转  - 停
- And turn. And turn. - And stop.
丽芙  我又不是你的私人超模
Liv, I'm not your personal supermodel.
哦  玛蒂  我从来没说过你是啊
Oh, Maddie, I never said you were.
你可是我的三维镜子
You are my 3-d mirror.
那好
Okay.
你的三维镜子就要辞职不干了
Well, your 3D mirror is about to quit.
我这周要和灰熊队打一场比赛
I have a big game against the grizzlies this week
这双脚将是要上篮球场的
and these feet need to be on a basketball court.
- 所以  - 啊  我可要提醒你
- So... - Ah! Need I remind you
这次时尚的小短会算是次报复
that this little fashion sesh is payback
报复你把我最喜欢的羊绒衫混在别的衣服里面  洗的缩水缩成这样
for you tossing my favorite cashmere sweater in the laundry.
好吧
Okay.
为什么女孩子都这么痴迷于鞋子啊
Why do girls get so excited about shoes?
我的意思是  它们不过就是用来垫脚的嘛
I mean, they're just things to put on your feet
这样你踩到一坨大粪就不会得钩虫病了
so that if you step in dog poop you don't get hookworm.
玛蒂  一双合适的高跟鞋能让一个女孩感到魔力四射
Maddie, the right pair of heels can make a girl feel magical.
而她的妈妈也可以借走享受享受魔力
And her mother when she borrows them.
站住
Stop.
你们为什么要拖着一堆树枝穿堂入室啊
Why are you dragging tree branches through the house?
如果穿过房子而不是绕过房子的话
Going through the house instead of around
能让我们提前 27 步抵达削木机
gets us to the wood chipper 27 steps faster.
顺便还能让我们在厨房喝一杯又冰又甜的柠檬水
Plus we can stop in the kitchen for a nice, cold glass of lemonade.
对哦  不过这还会在房子里留下一堆等着某人收拾的烂叶子
Right. It also creates a trail of leaves for someone to clean up later.
噢
Oh.
好了  把东西收拾好吧
Okay, well, let's... let's wrap this up.
别这样  玛蒂  难道这里就没有一点点合你口味的东西么
Come on, Maddie, there's not even a little part of you that's enjoying this?
等一下  丽芙  让我想一想
Oh, hold on, Liv. Let me check real quick.
呃  一点都没有
Um... no.
真的吗
Seriously?
得了吧  玛蒂  你不能整辈子都只穿运动鞋啊
Okay, you can't wear sneakers for the rest of your life, Maddie.
你猜怎么着  你要激发你内心的光芒
You know what... you need to tap into your inner sparkle.
让你的小四眼好好欣赏欣赏  这双鞋
Feast your four eyes... on these!
我已经找到了最好的高跟鞋
I have found the perfect pumps.
哦  闻起来就像走在时尚最前沿的一碗布丁上一样
Oh! It's as if you were walking around in a bowl of high-fashion pudding.
好的  好的  你够了
Okay, okay, enough.
我会试穿它的
I will try them on.
好吧  但是要小心  你一旦把它撑大了我就穿不了了
Okay, just be careful, 'cause if you stretch 'em I can't wear 'em.
你们有十秒的时间
You guys have ten seconds.
抓紧看吧
Look quick.
10  9  8
10, 9, 8...
哇  我的亲娘啊
Whoa, mama.
原来这就是由内而外的光芒啊
Hello, inner sparkle.
我爱死这双鞋了
I love these shoes.
我真讨厌这双鞋
I hate these shoes.
好吧  你能骗一个假小子穿上女装  但你永远没法让她美丽动人的
Well, you can lead a tomboy to designer shoes but you can't make her shimmer.